gangster: n.   歹徒,强盗, Chicago: n.   芝加哥(美国城市)
Lesson 14. A noble gangster. There was a time when the owners of shops and businesses in Chicago
第14课。贵族黑帮。曾经有一段时间
gangster: n.   歹徒,强盗, protection: n.   保护
that to pay large sums of money. Two gangsters in return for protection. If the money was not paid
支付大笔钱。两个黑帮以换取保护。如果没有付款
gangster: n.   歹徒,强盗, promptly: adv. 准时地, destroy: v.   毁掉;消灭
promptly, the gangsters would quickly put a man out of business by destroying his shop.
枪手很快就会迅速通过摧毁他的商店来使一个人失业。
protection: n.   保护
Obtaining protection money is not a modern crime. As long ago as the 14th century, an Englishman,
获得保护资金不是现代犯罪。直到14世纪，英国人
remarkable: adj. 不寻常的
Sir John Hockwood made the remarkable discovery that people would rather pay large sums of money
约翰·霍克伍德爵士（Sir John Hockwood）提出了一个非凡的发现，人们宁愿付出大笔钱
gangster: n.   歹徒,强盗, destroy: v.   毁掉;消灭
than have their life. Work destroyed by gangsters. 600 years ago, Sir Johann Hockwood arrived in
而不是拥有他们的生命。被黑帮摧毁的工作。600年前，约翰·霍克伍德爵士到达
Florence: n.   佛罗伦萨(意大利城市)
Italy with a band of soldiers and settled near Florence. He soon made a name for himself and came
意大利有一群士兵，在佛罗伦萨附近定居。他很快就为自己起了名字，来了
city-state: n.   (古代)城邦
to be known to the Italians as Giovanni Accuto. Whenever the Italian city-states were at war with
意大利人称为Giovanni Accuto。每当意大利城市国家与
hire: v.   租出,雇给, prince: n.   君主,诸候
each other, Hockwood used to hire his soldiers to princes who were willing to pay the high price
彼此，霍克伍德曾经雇用他的士兵到愿意付出高价的王子
he demanded. In times of peace, when business was bad, Hockwood and his men would march into a city
他要求。在和平时期，当生意不好时，霍克伍德和他的士兵将进军一个城市
protection: n.   保护
state and, after burning down a few farms, would offer to go away protection money was paid to them.
州并烧毁了几个农场后，将付款给他们提供保护资金。
Hockwood made large sums of money in this way. In spite of this, the Italians regarded him as a
霍克伍德以这种方式赚了大笔钱。尽管如此，意大利人还是将他视为
Florentine: n.   佛罗伦萨人, funeral: n.   葬礼
sort of hero. When he died at the age of 80, the Florentines gave him a state funeral and had a
有点英雄。当他80岁时去世时，佛罗伦萨给了他一场葬礼，并有一个
dedicate: v.   奉献,题献给, memory: n.   纪念, valiant: adj. 英勇的
pictured with as dedicated to the memory of the most valiant soldier and most notable leader.
描绘的是献给最英勇的士兵和最著名的领导者的记忆。
Senior Giovanni Hockwood.
高级乔瓦尼·霍克伍德（Giovanni Hockwood）。